Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let me just, read… let me just read, make sure I understood what's supposed to happen next.
Kostadis Roussos: You ready? Yes. There's… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Alright. So, you, you,
Kostadis Roussos: You have now secured… so, Solomoned Rousak has given you a spellbook. Let me, give you that spell book, Nicholas.
Kostadis Roussos: Which you can cast as…
Kostadis Roussos: I think you can cast them as spells, but you can cast them as scrolls, so we'll say you can cast them as scrolls, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
Kostadis Roussos: Where is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Nick, where should I put this? In Discord, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold by.
Kostadis Roussos: the original, no, I mean, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You get a portion of greater fuel.
Kostadis Roussos: And he also provides you the following scrolls.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm listening. Okay, they're in the D&D chat, in the Discord chat.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Do you see them?
Kostadis Roussos: Love, Roussos, and… I thought. Thank you. Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the situation as it is, is that you now have secured your allies.
Kostadis Roussos: But all of the allies are going to help you.
Kostadis Roussos: After you get rid of dengue.
Kostadis Roussos: The Giants.
Kostadis Roussos: Insane. The giant that was Sithm. I thought it would do that.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you got… Wasn't the resident help us, actually?
Kostadis Roussos: Shouldn't the Revenant be there because that's what she thinks there? The Revenant has gone on a lunatic assign… has gone on a lunatic basis. Shouldn't she be there because that's… should she think kill it?
Kostadis Roussos: She isn't here right now.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so… there is another giant… Oh, so, so, so, so let me explain. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: There… this… okay, so you… so to remind you what's going on. The Sith Markane is currently being… the Sith Markane currently has a forge.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, yeah, before just search them.
Kostadis Roussos: Which is dedicated to some demonic giant god, not important. You got… what's been going on is they've been building materials that they've been shipping to Miramindra, but they're going to use to stage their assault on the surface world. You managed to stop one of those transfers.
Kostadis Roussos: Every… all the factions in Meramedra are willing… in Sithm are willing to help you as long as you get rid of the current giants that are running the show.
Kostadis Roussos: You said plural? Plural. Yes, plural.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So what you got rid of was the fire giant that was taking the… How many fire giants have we taken about?
Kostadis Roussos: How many fire giants are we talking about? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Undetermined amount.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, this is a good question.
Kostadis Roussos: Why did we have been the group to know about it?
Kostadis Roussos: What did we get back? What? Nothing. What did we actually get out of doing all that?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so you're trying to take over Miramidra? Yes, and otherwise that's helpful, perhaps.
Kostadis Roussos: I, if I remember correctly, were the last… Sounds… Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Okay, so let's continue. No, no, no, no, I mean, let me… Nick. Okay, so, so let me remind you. You, you, you, you managed to…
Kostadis Roussos: get the… the… the fire giants from Merameda? What? Let me close my book. Yeah. We managed to get the fire giant, right? The fire giants…
Kostadis Roussos: Solar Deathrooms Act.
Kostadis Roussos: casts a spell, does his thing with the franchise. Yay! We'll beat you down. You're, you're now thinking yourself, you now hear from, you now get information from the Emerald Enclave. From the Emerald Enclave, and your various allies, and the Mind Flayers.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Yes, and what you've learned is that the fire giants are building these devices that they're going to use to lay waste on the surface world.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, right, we need this response. Yes, and so then… so while you… so your job was to go and do something about that. Right. While you were going down there to do something about that, you met Alder.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm kidding. A halfling rogue who notoriously imprisoned Wolf.
Kostadis Roussos: Bing.
Kostadis Roussos: And, she explained that, she sent a whole bunch of other adventurers into, into, Medzel Daronsin.
Kostadis Roussos: They didn't come back. No, no, she… but there was… but she then realized there was another problem.
Kostadis Roussos: One of the demons grasped, had a backup plan, and he was gonna show up at Mbidrav.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So her… the original plan was… she… she… the original plan, which was going great, was that a whole bunch of heroes were gonna go into the Underdark.
Kostadis Roussos: They were… they were very close to putting together a plan, which was going to attract all of the demons into Menzo Baronson, where they would all die, and the problem with the demons would just go…
Kostadis Roussos: But what she noticed, but what happened was… took another way. Yeah, she discovered that grass may have another plant.
Kostadis Roussos: And so you became her Plan B.
Kostadis Roussos: Of course. To go into Miramidra and make sure that if grass shows up, grass is defeated. Right, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Your concerns are, you need to get into Nirmidra to stop breast. Whether Narmedra is… belongs to the fire giants.
Kostadis Roussos: or not.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a problem for another day. Okay. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: just… To keep that in mind.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: But you also like to destroy Marameda, because that's where the fire giants are currently. If grass shows up.
Kostadis Roussos: It doesn't really matter.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? He's powerful enough that he's going to cause chaos and mayhem with or without magical devices. But if you can defeat him.
Kostadis Roussos: then the… and your allies can destroy enough of Mare Nidra, then the threat of the fire giants, the disease-infected fire giants goes away, okay? The other theory you have is that
Kostadis Roussos: The fire giants are… have been driven insane by breast.
Kostadis Roussos: So if you defeat Grast, they'll be fine. Or they'll be less crazy. Yes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so, they might be more reasonable, they might be less willing to cause mayhem and chaos.
Kostadis Roussos: The fire giants. You know, the fire giants are not, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: They're, they're, they're, they're, yeah, but they're not unreasonable. How about I put it that way? Okay. Right? They're, they're…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they're violates, but they're not insane.
Kostadis Roussos: these guys are sort of like fire giants to the 20th degree. Yeah. Right? So it's more of an extreme fire giant than normal fire giant.
Kostadis Roussos: And so the way to think about it is that the fire giants have been driven bad by frost.
Kostadis Roussos: You need to defeat the Fire Giants, and more importantly, you need to make sure that if Brass shows up, you defeat him.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I know how the session… the story ends. Well, you've been facing grass left, right, and center.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Yeah. So, don't you want to have one last chance at it? Yeah, yeah. No? Well, not after a war.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, again, remember, Everybody has got objectives.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the people in Hillspar… Do you know what the booth have done? Well, they said to the Reverend that grass killed Solomon. Oh…
Kostadis Roussos: It was a good opportunity. Yes, it was.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know if memory's fair. I, you know, maybe. I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't think I have any further questions, rather than… So, so… early link?
Kostadis Roussos: Overbread. What? The wind… the word to do all that is that we have the overbraid. Yes. And a grass is no longer inside of, you know, the demons are, sent back to where they came from. What you found out was
Kostadis Roussos: that the demons were brought back into the… because of some magical effect known as the Blink.
Kostadis Roussos: Whose origin is unknown.
Kostadis Roussos: It was from Falmart's. What? It was from Thomas. Yes, that's true. Oh, fuck, that's where I got the idea, isn't it? Yup.
Kostadis Roussos: They're literally calling it Link.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm speaking the lights, the ferouses went on and off, that's where I got it, but I probably… my choice of the word, the blink comes from there. Yeah, right. Yeah, fair. So I go, where did I come? I was a pretty cool name. I was very impressed with myself now.
Kostadis Roussos: impressed with myself for stealing a good idea. I'm sorry. No, I'm not… I mean, you should be sorry. You should be proud of yourself, actually. Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, according to… I was just going to see how many prefer Janice there are.
Kostadis Roussos: According to the best information Roussevaez Quilburn has.
Kostadis Roussos: There were a total of 12 fire giants.
Kostadis Roussos: Two are dead. So we have 10 to kill.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and so the one thing you know about fire guns is that if you kill off the head, the rest fall.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Right? You've already spooked them out by killing two of their kind group. So if you just killed, the Denegore.
Kostadis Roussos: the lead fire giants. Okay, we…
Kostadis Roussos: You could get that they might just run away.
Kostadis Roussos: Run away, or join our own?
Kostadis Roussos: No, that thing is very unlikely.
Kostadis Roussos: unlikely. Well, we had many, many, like, scenarios. Yeah, I just said, I said, you know, I was gonna say no, and then I was like.
Kostadis Roussos: Very unlikely. We have the Stone of Zions, we have the old people, we have the five that have lost. There's many unlikings and arguments. I mean, there's the whole, I don't understand the liches…
Kostadis Roussos: And what ghosts are.
Kostadis Roussos: the whole, we had to do a deal with it. The whole deal with the Arcano one? Yes, there's been a lot of…
Kostadis Roussos: Ups and downs. Ups and downs in this adventure. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So… You're gonna see that.
Kostadis Roussos: But we're not passionate enough to succeed.
Kostadis Roussos: All right Okay, so, so there's two ways into his palace.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay? The first way… is through his palace directly. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: The second way is you could enter through the fame of Loth.
Kostadis Roussos: You've been there before. It was that big cavern dungeon that looked like a spider, now known as the Forge of Sutra.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that one. Yes. I was thinking about the web, we are already putting… Yeah, so again. Okay, so that… those are your two choices. It says to get into there.
Kostadis Roussos: He… Rosaviah says he can cast, gaseous form, so you can enter it through the tunnels. Yeah. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Or do you want to do that, or do you want to go through the main door?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, let's go through the gas station for another.
Kostadis Roussos: Genesis 4 method? Yeah. It is.
Kostadis Roussos: Why would you shut this down the door?
Kostadis Roussos: I think it's really good. What?
Kostadis Roussos: One thing you do know is that the faint… this is where you're going to find all the weapons you need for right leader.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so…
Kostadis Roussos: She's not… so they're not… so… so you're… that's her fine? We're gonna go through the fate of loss? I get, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: The gorgeous intro.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Already.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: We need to…
Kostadis Roussos: You need to stick to your flight today.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you arrive… okay, now I've read enough about this, so I can now roll on it. Okay, so now you are going to go into the House Morgan's… Horkain's Ruins.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And… air…
Kostadis Roussos: There.
Kostadis Roussos: Give me a moment, guys, because I have to load… I have to… I have to load something. I thought I had it… I had something… I thought I had loaded something, but I had not. My bad.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's go whoops in quick, quick, quick.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: It means that…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait till you end.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, it's here…
Kostadis Roussos: So, you manage to… you could turn into gaseous form, and as a result of the gaseous form, you're able to…
Kostadis Roussos: sneak in to the forge of Sutra. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: The Forge of Sutra.
Kostadis Roussos: is…
Kostadis Roussos: the thing that… the thing that, that you immediately… you immediately realize is this is big, right? This is, like, not some small…
Kostadis Roussos: vanilla operation, so let me just show you what it looks like.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys, should see that, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, relatively, you know… And, what is it that you're… what else do you see here?
Kostadis Roussos: Good.
Kostadis Roussos: The heat hits before the light does, then both at once.
Kostadis Roussos: That cavern the size of a keeps great hall. Ceilings lost in smoke, the floor grid of forged channels were molten rock, runs controlled by azer, who move around the heat like they were born from it, because they were. On the western wall, a row of finished frames, steels and darkwood, each one of eight feet long and shaped like a huge crossbow with a serpent's jaw.
Kostadis Roussos: The three are crated and stacked near a loading dock at the far end. Four more are half-assembled on the floor, their binding rings not set. The azer didn't look up. They are not curious. They are busy working.
Kostadis Roussos: the scale. This is industrial, not a workshop.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, this is a major, yeah, production thing. The engines that you've been told about are easily identifiable. They're oversized Balista or Hellfire project files.
Kostadis Roussos: You do notice that the serpents are designed as unusual.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Right? You notice the crates from the previous shipment, right? And you notice 4 that are still unfinished.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, you guys, we'll push you guys, but you guys, good things.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you guys already have.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys sort of emerge over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: you can see that this… if you can destroy the forge, or at least destroy the people who are manning the Forge, you'll… you'll break the fire giant's ability to build more of the siege weapons.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm thinking to work the wounds.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, cool, I'll throw it back toward you, but…
Kostadis Roussos: I rolled a fever, never mind.
Kostadis Roussos: I legitimately gonna throw a beer bottle at it, that's the best… it worked once, it worked again. We're gonna have to get into a fight.
Kostadis Roussos: She wants us in a bottle of cocktail.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you say Molotov content? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's another option. Yeah, can we do an author? No, I don't think so.
Kostadis Roussos: But, how to make a law of… Pretty often.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay, so there are four Azer acolytes, two Azur priests, one helmed Sahorer, and 2 salamanders.
Kostadis Roussos: Doesn't sound like males.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so… Do you want to take her out?
Kostadis Roussos: That's a good question.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it would be good to stop the production.
Kostadis Roussos: But if we just go kill the main guy, there's not gonna be production, right? What? If we go kill the main pipe giant.
Kostadis Roussos: There's not gonna be a production rate.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we don't actually know where he is.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I would have to go there and ask them if the way he was.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that your plan?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna go… that is your plan, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you agree with the plan? Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Just want to make sure that that is the plan.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you, huh?
Kostadis Roussos: Agent.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just, put everything that's here.
Kostadis Roussos: Listen.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just see something…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. So all of them are just one sprint you're gonna wear, right?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry? I'm just one spirit guide you in a way, right? And one spirit. Oh, oh!
Kostadis Roussos: I think my question was right. No, no, it is, it is, it is, it is. I'm just, I'm just trying to, like, I'm just, I just need to,
Kostadis Roussos: I just… what you're seeing me is I'm trying to add colors to these guys so you know who they are.
Kostadis Roussos: So, let's what the stat's gonna be.
Kostadis Roussos: -
Kostadis Roussos: So we should roll our initiative, or are they gonna be talkative?
Kostadis Roussos: I'd like to put everybody down so you can make an informed decision.
Kostadis Roussos: 15th?
Kostadis Roussos: What are they?
Kostadis Roussos: Are these all fire guns? No. No fire guns here? No. What are they? I'm about to… I'm going to redescribe it in a second.
Kostadis Roussos: What are you more?
Kostadis Roussos: The ones without the red?
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: They're Azure Acolytes. 8 of 3, 46 each. Oh, that's like one Spirit Guardian, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, with a good role, yes. And, the Azur priests are more powerful.
Kostadis Roussos: There. Definitely buffer.
Kostadis Roussos: There's the Helm Horror.
Kostadis Roussos: And then there are fire salamanders.
Kostadis Roussos: Oops, there are a few of these holes.
Kostadis Roussos: Those 13 these days.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: My own door is standing over here. Okie dokie.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys sort of are seeing the scene from over here.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it that you wish to do? To the north over here, it is a double door that is giant-sized. Just make sure you know that. What are these?
Kostadis Roussos: Fire cylinders.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Meeting?
Kostadis Roussos: Got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay. So, what is your move?
Kostadis Roussos: Good question.
Kostadis Roussos: Should we ask investment players who can find resigning?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you could do that? I must even want to do that.
Kostadis Roussos: And we want to ask the guy to come with the comparison with scientists.
Kostadis Roussos: Or I can test RBD and I and just, like, move it around for a while.
Kostadis Roussos: Both closed companies, St. Louis.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, come with two, Rompins for the two sides? Yeah, you can just see true sides, but true side doesn't… TrueStream, true thing. Can you find a sign like that? Oh, no, no, that you won't be able to.
Kostadis Roussos: So, what? It's a hell of a war.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a… you've met one of those before, right? They're constructs That are obedient lizards.
Kostadis Roussos: And to other, so, it could be targeted.
Kostadis Roussos: Generally not.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I have a great spell to actually just, like, kill the Fire Dragon.
Kostadis Roussos: So the only other…
Kostadis Roussos: I… can I cast an eye spell, and then I just go, like, looking around? Yeah, you can cast the Arcane I.
Kostadis Roussos: I wonder…
Kostadis Roussos: Do well.
Kostadis Roussos: Random question.
Kostadis Roussos: Can I put a stone in it?
Kostadis Roussos: Like, just, like, a tie on a little stun? No.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it that you want to accomplish, Fred? I want to accomplish it that I basically want to have, like, an eye… I basically want to have a mini drone I can go fly around and ask people from distance, hey, where's the,
Kostadis Roussos: That we're panning about.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you have a vague idea of where it is, or is it anywhere, too? Like… No, no, no, no, no, she do know where he is. He's either in here, or in his palace, which… and the entrance to his palace is through… is down these stairs. Oh, yeah, I'm gonna cast our canine and go look where it is. Okay, is that what you… yeah, I'm sorry, yeah, yeah, you do… Oh, okay, yeah, I'm gonna cast our canine. I just don't know exactly where he is. Yeah, I'm gonna go cast RK9 and look where he is.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: And… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, and then we can just cast Passport to get there.
Kostadis Roussos: award.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, this is easy.
Kostadis Roussos: Otis is ridiculously, she's gonna cast.
Kostadis Roussos: And then the black tentacles, because that seems like a useful story to be identified brand.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Is it thoroughly.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'll do that.
Kostadis Roussos: You still have to deal with these guys in the reviewer eventually.
Kostadis Roussos: No? Why? Because they're not fire gents.
Kostadis Roussos: So… I hope that you understand everything. Yeah?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you, I'm just telling… I'm just telling you, these guys, these guys over here might be a problem, but I just want you to… The hole lasts for an hour.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just… we need to go in, go up. It's a quick one and done, you mentioned that. I want to have full HP and full spouse looks for you. Okay, that's fine, that's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Where is it? What happened to you, Twain?
Kostadis Roussos: Huh?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, right, right, right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: What the hell?
Kostadis Roussos: No, that wasn't even, I should've said that.
Kostadis Roussos: I need a compass.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You… tell me what the duration of an RTMI is.
Kostadis Roussos: An hour. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, understand where there's a… there's a fire giant sized door over here, I think you're gonna need to send your… you're gonna send it there first. You send it there first, and, it's, nowhere… he's nowhere to be found. The stairs. Down the stairs?
Kostadis Roussos: Stairs.
Kostadis Roussos: Down the stairs, leads to… another caves.
Kostadis Roussos: down the street over here.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, I'm reading up the map.
Kostadis Roussos: That is better.
Kostadis Roussos: What do you expect? No.
Kostadis Roussos: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: your magic eye… Leads you down to here.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sure Whitney was quickly gathered in Palace.
Kostadis Roussos: Is there a fire guide? Yes there is. Is it a piece of fire guide? Yes, there is.
Kostadis Roussos: Goodbye.
Kostadis Roussos: path vaults would get to a place where I can avoid doing impair combat.
Kostadis Roussos: In front of you?
Kostadis Roussos: And you guys can… if you guys can sneak across… Just pass fastball, I get to the stairs, and my… Pass wall means you go… creates a hole, and you need that teleport spell.
Kostadis Roussos: You have artificial abilities to create magic, you have pass without trace, you have a wide variety of techniques and skills.
Kostadis Roussos: you have gaseous… you can cast another instance of gaseous form. Does that work for all of us?
Kostadis Roussos: And I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: -Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so can I do this, Assassin's Creed style, where I gather all the enemies up into a ball, and then cast Sleep on them? So, gaseous form,
Kostadis Roussos: Gases from none.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what I can do… hold on, what I can do is…
Kostadis Roussos: I can… it can make the following meaning.
Kostadis Roussos: They just read about the gaseous form spell. So they cast the magic users, more surveys' magic users cast the gaseous form on.
Kostadis Roussos: We can say… That, up to here, you're all in gases form, except for Belfort.
Kostadis Roussos: To cast Arcane Eye, you have to go… Yeah, or I can just cast…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, we're using every single one of these callbooks right now. Yeah, this one. Is that what your plan is? Yeah. Okay, so your plan is to basically
Kostadis Roussos: Float along as a… as a gas.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: If you… Long… A longer… To be gas use.
Kostadis Roussos: And then… You arrive in his cups.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so we can put one that we've got here, and…
Kostadis Roussos: Mine puts it in my head.
Kostadis Roussos: They're, they're a little bit boxier than words.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: What on…
Kostadis Roussos: He burns, and then kill him. What?
Kostadis Roussos: convert.
Kostadis Roussos: So they're gonna be dead, but…
Kostadis Roussos: The bird? The bird. Why?
Kostadis Roussos: They're annoying.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we're making for it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: There's, like, 4 helm borders.
Kostadis Roussos: That are kind of, like, so he's sleeping over here,
Kostadis Roussos: May not be sleeping over here.
Kostadis Roussos: We've got a guard over here.
Kostadis Roussos: A couple of darns quickly here.
Kostadis Roussos: Courses, other people.
Kostadis Roussos: And that's an addition.
Kostadis Roussos: In addition…
Kostadis Roussos: It, I'm assuming things won't start getting good.
Kostadis Roussos: So we can get excited to expand it.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: So, kind of very excited to stand in.
Kostadis Roussos: Can this one guy on that, like, right there be, like, one place over? Yeah, so let me just… One square over, like, I'd really appreciate that. Really? I… You know, now that you made it, like, so obvious that that's where you would escape wanting to be… Like, do you know how much it would make my life suck?
Kostadis Roussos: So much easier.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
Kostadis Roussos: I wonder if I think so.
Kostadis Roussos: Edward's black tentacles. Tentacles, so at 20 foot square on the ground that you can see with thin range. For federation, these tentacles trim the ground into difficult terrain. Each creature in that area will face a strange saving throw. On a sale, there takes 3D bludging damage, and it has restrained condition until the spell ends.
Kostadis Roussos: A creature can also make the saves to enters or end its turn that a creature must save only one per turn. A strange creature can take an action to make its strength, but it's Jack against its quality 19.
Kostadis Roussos: I feel it for 5 times, it's gonna be, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Every time, that's not gonna be a bad work, and the fire tank just wants to know what?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, no doubt.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Maybe we don't want to congrat.
Kostadis Roussos: They, they, we don't want to do that, and they will dispute.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, this is where Gendor is.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and just so that… because this is… can't be this easy, of course.
Kostadis Roussos: public and civil.
Kostadis Roussos: But you have potential allies.
Kostadis Roussos: Away! I'm about to show you.
Kostadis Roussos: So, just to be clear, this encounter has potential islands, you just have to know where to get them.
Kostadis Roussos: And you also have… what's her name?
Kostadis Roussos: All of our husbands.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, there are 2 fire giants, and 3 stone giants.
Kostadis Roussos: The fire giants are clearly, the cast masters here.
Kostadis Roussos: And the stone giants are clearly in shackles.
Kostadis Roussos: Fair enough.
Kostadis Roussos: Boom.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Oh, I have a really funny idea. What? Yes, here it goes. You might have an idea. Yes. Can I do something?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, ignore me.
Kostadis Roussos: I would unmuted, son.
Kostadis Roussos: so you can blink. Okay, go, just go for it, tell me what it is.
Kostadis Roussos: Can somebody classify for me so that I can basically…
Kostadis Roussos: Because I have an idea, because it lasts for one minute, my idea is I can't blink.
Kostadis Roussos: run… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: run over.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, get over, have some trees, blink, get… cut the one stroke giant loose.
Kostadis Roussos: go back and either run over, cut another one, lose. Okay, do you have control over where Blink lands you? I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, well, it wasn't required using the term plan, so if that would be already on that one. At the end of your next term, and when the store ends, you're,
Kostadis Roussos: Unoccupied space of your choice within 10 feet of the space. Again, it's almost no unoccupied spaces available within the drains that you appear in the nearest unoccupied… Okay, so you have control over the exit.
Kostadis Roussos: Can't you there?
Kostadis Roussos: So, walking through your part. My idea is I…
Kostadis Roussos: My idea is that I… Basically, I want to…
Kostadis Roussos: Draws out against these depots like the Creed does, have passes our trade.
Kostadis Roussos: Fine, get over.
Kostadis Roussos: try and get over, cut, and then cut to each one of the stone giants flew secretly. Who's got…
Kostadis Roussos: It's the doorway accounting department.
Kostadis Roussos: Where'd you go? Oh, hold on, I went to his question.
Kostadis Roussos: Over here.
Kostadis Roussos: You're in gaseous form, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Where is the closest spot to the Giants I can drop out without anyone noticing?
Kostadis Roussos: In April, don't remember.
Kostadis Roussos: I wouldn't be good, I'm being honest. No.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, that might work. If we drop out, we have a round of prep dinner.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, the thing is, the Giants… okay, so…
Kostadis Roussos: role your insight, or investigation. Insider Investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Which one?
Kostadis Roussos: Which are one tomorrow? Oh, sorry, sorry. 22. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: You have a couple of insights. One is that the two fire giants are looking very boring.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, they're not looking at the contacts, yeah. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You also can hear, the giant… the fire giant snoring in the background.
Kostadis Roussos: So, thank them. So, that's it.
Kostadis Roussos: I might, I don't, I might want to cut this.
Kostadis Roussos: Would there be any disadvantage to have if it…
Kostadis Roussos: if it's asleep and I cast the spell that kind of makes it, like…
Kostadis Roussos: would it automatically fail, or is it fail if I can't
Kostadis Roussos: If it's incapacitated. Yeah. It's whatever the rules are for incapacitated.
Kostadis Roussos: Do I think it automatically is there, or… Yeah, I mean, unless it's… yeah, well, what kind of, let me just check the condition incapacitated.
Kostadis Roussos: Conditioned, incapacitated.
Kostadis Roussos: You can't take, any action, Bonsai. If you are incapacitive, you have disadvantage on the roll.
Kostadis Roussos: Your concentration doesn't… Oh, it's okay, we don't want… What?
Kostadis Roussos: I have two very useful things to do, and I don't want to cut the stone jam, please, because that'll… because we have a very unique opportunity with the fire guy. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I might just, like, literally start teleporting around everywhere.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that what I?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, wait, I'm confused.
Kostadis Roussos: We're seeing death somewhere else.
Kostadis Roussos: So we can all move near electrons to ions. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I have a different idea. I just want to make sure that when you're in gaseous form.
Kostadis Roussos: You can't touch anything. Yes, I know. We have some… not all of us, some of us should be able to know before. Yes. Release them, talk to them. Yes. Make a discussion.
Kostadis Roussos: Not all of us, because… No, I have another idea, trying to explain. So, then as those in front of bed.
Kostadis Roussos: Valencia.
Kostadis Roussos: They do. Right. So, transportation rules. Actually, can I explain my idea? My idea is that
Kostadis Roussos: I believe that because it's incapacitated, I… because it's asleep, I can give it the… I can cast a spell, and it'll give it the… it'll cause it to take damage, and it'll also give it the fire giant to respond condition, and other creatures around it. You stand on the gedge, and basically just start…
Kostadis Roussos: attacking it. I… I stand, because I have a range, I can see it. I stand somewhere over here while I catapult. So you're talking about the main zone? Let's speak. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Because you're gonna have an ability, basically, to attack it with a full random surprise, with advantage, while it's in data. That's the second part of the plan. No, no, no, but here's the thing that if you attack it.
Kostadis Roussos: But I… Yeah, but you're saying that's also used a stone jives to create a structure. Yeah, no, but if we do that, the giant will wake up. You can do it in the sequence.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I want… if I… for you to spend time first, the main guy will wake up. No, but you could free the… you can do the Fire Giant, and then the Stem Giant.
Kostadis Roussos: Did that work?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't…
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, so you go create Cap… I didn't finish what I was trying to say. After I do that, I cast Misty Step or Blink or something to go start freeing the giants. Right, I was saying that two of you could go here with the fire hand.
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody deals, I think just go run a… for example, your foulware doesn't have range attacks.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, the elder can go try and figure out a way to… So the elder can go help create chaos on the stone? We need to do the attack on the Fire Giant first, so it doesn't wake up. So, here's what I'm suggesting. Wait. So, wait… And we were about them.
Kostadis Roussos: We talked to the stone giants, and let them know that… don't attack and do Russell. They're not gonna attack them. The stone giants are in shackles, so they're not gonna… Yeah, we're trying to free them. They're gonna free them first, and then gonna…
Kostadis Roussos: Are they smart enough to understand those instructions?
Kostadis Roussos: Are we able to file them attacks?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but I mean, yes, you are. Yes, the only thing is that the fire guides might note it, that's the only… Yeah, that's the… But they're working their own steel, so you're not gonna recognize.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and these are self-checks you will have to make.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, perfect. So, if…
Kostadis Roussos: with Sweden, and then wait, and it's gonna signal to start the chaos. It can't be your plan, and we're all gonna be here willing to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Look, there's one guy, one guard at the front that I don't think will be able to speak, that I don't want to risk our entire plan on. Look, most of the…
Kostadis Roussos: Most of our,
Kostadis Roussos: I don't want to risk our entire plan on one saving throw. That's the issue. I want to… There's no savings throw.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's also trying to reset button.
Kostadis Roussos: No, because we're industrial.
Kostadis Roussos: How are we gonna sleep forward at that point? I predict us and developer.
Kostadis Roussos: And move there, we went, misstep… By the way, I'm assuming you've all taken the long runs, right? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Misstep and move there. It'd be better if we only free, right, if we give bikes the chain.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, there will be coming immediately, so now I'm gonna talk about. Okay, yeah, so give me the details for the public website.
Kostadis Roussos: I… why would I need to talk to our tree because I can make me step right over.
Kostadis Roussos: We need to do the same secretly. There's that?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no. Oh, I don't… I think you misunderstand my plan. We do this simultaneously. Can I show you what I draw? No, no. Here's my plan. Can I explain? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys drop out somewhere here. I don't go where you are. I stay here, cast a spell on the giant.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, cast a spell to stop the giant, you guys attack, and then I meet… I'm going to be on the same… different… the same steps, or just different…
Kostadis Roussos: Why would we see the Stone Giants first?
Kostadis Roussos: Because then we don't have to come back to freedom.
Kostadis Roussos: My issue with that is that…
Kostadis Roussos: Most of the parts can go up here, because there's still gas from. Why don't we do it simultaneously, though, and have the 3D deals?
Kostadis Roussos: A creature's one of the big damaging, and if we can have her have that advantage, and a free, like, revolt on the Giant, that's, like, a free 40 or 50. It's…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I'm gonna keep this second copy of that.
Kostadis Roussos: That's why…
Kostadis Roussos: Free the stone giants, then do the rest of your plumbing to the stone giants. Yeah, free the stone giants, I can do that by myself. I can get… me and the Albert can do that. But we need you to do the Yakos first. That's why I dropped out, like, over here, because I have to bring the cage, so… so, to understand.
Kostadis Roussos: Olberg… okay, so let's say Olberg stays here to tell you… Or, like, that's one of these giants, like, over here. Like, that's just… we just ran to that over here. So, all the rest of us…
Kostadis Roussos: Or, like, no, no, like, I mean right next to the giant. It's gonna be not able to move. So, it comes inside here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I cast the thing that's basically, like, right here, so… and you move here.
Kostadis Roussos: No, sure, I… I need to find a good spot for people, because I need to…
Kostadis Roussos: the airlines side.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to be in… can I… can you… can I move these real quick? Because I need to… because you might need to drop by in a little bit of a different spot, that makes sense.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, where's my… the sign here, where's the lines? Where's my lines Google?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't even know why.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So I can sneak a little bit of a… R.
Kostadis Roussos: Can I show you where to drop off?
Kostadis Roussos: somewhere, like, Right here.
Kostadis Roussos: Because my… it's a… it's a 20 foot by 20 foot. If I place it right there.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, on my thing. If you… if I place it right here, that gets the Fire Giant.
Kostadis Roussos: And it allowed me To go from here, line of sight, Right.
Kostadis Roussos: perfectly here, so I'm not in range of that, so I can cast it, and then jump, and then go get one of the giants.
Kostadis Roussos: Anywhere? Yes. That one?
Kostadis Roussos: I believe so, but… I don't see anyone.
Kostadis Roussos: I dare to re-explain it to you.
Kostadis Roussos: That's… Can we explain the plan? Yes, sir. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Edwards Black Pentacles, make… cover that 20 foot square on the ground, you can see within range, so 4 by 5. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: For the duration… Just for the record, so that there's no confusion, we will use the grid and not the underlay grid, so that'll make the grid more visible. What's your grid? I'm about to find.
Kostadis Roussos: And just, like, you know, and… Oh, that's good, yeah, that was the one I was… Okay. So… We'll use the green, we'll use the green…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, just, just in case. So, what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna cast it right here.
Kostadis Roussos: So that the giant gets affected. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Then, what is going to happen?
Kostadis Roussos: I, using lines, I'm gonna cast it on this spot, but it can spread it over here, right? Yeah. So, if I show you, line of sight from here allows me to be…
Kostadis Roussos: Basically, right, right over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Around here, because I have the 90-foot tapping range. Right. Alright, understand? Yep. So, then…
Kostadis Roussos: You can have the elder… can the elder flee one of the giants? Like, to bite their chin off, or something?
Kostadis Roussos: He could… he can definitely try.
Kostadis Roussos: So I'm gonna be over here, I'm gonna cast that spell, They're gonna drop off beard.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, because… because the Giants are gonna be…
Kostadis Roussos: They're gonna drop off, right? Yeah, they're gonna drop off, like, basically, they're gonna be… all drop off, like, where they… in a way they can attack the Fire Giant. Okay. Because the Fire Giant's gonna be incapacitated, and it's gonna have the restraint conviction. Yep. So they're gonna have advantage of it, and…
Kostadis Roussos: While they're doing that, I'm… whilst they're that, I'm immediately gonna run over and start freeing the giants. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm also gonna have Blink on myself, that way I have an easier way of escaping so that they can't… so if the fire guys try and close the gap on me, they can't get me. Okay. Did that work? That is definitely a good point. That's definitely a workable plan. The outcome of which is ill-defined and unknowable at this time.
Kostadis Roussos: So let me go over it.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sweet.
Kostadis Roussos: Boom.
Kostadis Roussos: Here, I'm gonna draw a rectangle, so no.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, baby.
Kostadis Roussos: something large.
Kostadis Roussos: means this.
Kostadis Roussos: Get in a good… I also have to get in a good…
Kostadis Roussos: Something like… yeah, too. That way we do okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Basically, try and hard focus the fire giant.
Kostadis Roussos: codes.
Kostadis Roussos: We kind of get a little bit of a corner, so the best part is just to throw it as fast as possible.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm like, focus.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll do whatever we want. Alright, is that good?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me charge off some other ones, you'll have to see if your hands and get it.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that line of sight? Dad? Yes. The line actually line of sight? Do you see it, or, machine again?
Kostadis Roussos: Is that a line of sight?
Kostadis Roussos: From where you are, where folklore is right now? I'm just drawing the line. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that is what I'm gonna say. I'm actually gonna move like that, then, because…
Kostadis Roussos: Glad to be there.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I… well, now let me redraw one of the rectangles. I'm trying to draw a rectangle so that basically…
Kostadis Roussos: Easily obvious.
Kostadis Roussos: I wanna make this? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Like that?
Kostadis Roussos: I was mostly trying to sleep.
Kostadis Roussos: I was trying to see if there's a way I can get all of the, all these two enemies in here as well, without having to… How big is, how big is this thing? 4x5.
Kostadis Roussos: If any extra room, I'm just shoving off into the side of the corner.
Kostadis Roussos: So, according to the rules that I have defined, the monster has to be At least half.
Kostadis Roussos: But you could, do it that way. No, but then we can't attack it.
Kostadis Roussos: Agent.
Kostadis Roussos: Because it stays on the background.
Kostadis Roussos: Dana?
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody… two people use Melee.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll make it.
Kostadis Roussos: Rahul doesn't need to know.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, you can just… alright, except you're gonna be… actually, no, you can jump to corner if you need. Yes, you can walk. Alright, I'm good, we're good.
Kostadis Roussos: The rule is you can always navigate on the back. Alright, we're good. Ready, and everybody ready?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, yeah, although it's get a bill.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we're good.
Kostadis Roussos: You're good?
Kostadis Roussos: After I cast it, do I have movement to, do I have movement to run over, or… Right, so let's do one thing at a time. Okay, let's first roll… let's first get our initiative. Yeah, yeah, yeah, why don't we start, like, okay, so now that you… Can you tell me we gotta supply them?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna give you guys a pride.
Kostadis Roussos: Can we… did we get surprised on beforehand? Yeah, I'm gonna… I'm gonna declare for the purposes of this combat, you do the thing.
Kostadis Roussos: You've spent so much inordinate amount of time
Kostadis Roussos: It's a good plant. No, no, no, I can't know anything that says it's not.
Kostadis Roussos: That's good.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, my God, I gotta get in the Super Bowl.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Maybe? 20 yen.
Kostadis Roussos: Can't the elder free to stone guns?
Kostadis Roussos: We'll find out.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, this… this elder went from a simple, just random thing in the middle of the woods, to literally going to the depths of hell and back.
Kostadis Roussos: Moving to as it should be.
Kostadis Roussos: You did not expect that.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't belong, obviously.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see what this officially will appear that we don't outlining the type of book.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I'm sure that there's a witch.
Kostadis Roussos: You're so bitter of that.
Kostadis Roussos: You know the story of the Lich, right? Yeah, that's true. So what happened was, basically, we were fighting some, I forget what it was, and there was a couple skeletons, and we… and, you know, there was a skeleton, and we just left off this, oh, unimportant skeleton. We were trying to get this bile that could start a zombie plague.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a skeleton… was this originally planned from the beginning? The skeleton was a fucking rich.
Kostadis Roussos: That time stops, stole the vial, and teleported away.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's still biting about this.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: One of these different kinds is a lich.
Kostadis Roussos: You only can do that once. Like, you can't go for the class. Like, once something is done and it's a classic, you know, you've got to respect that. Are we good?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, but I haven't given all the Fire Giant's numbers. Also, you have…
Kostadis Roussos: to him and bend off. Oh, wait, if they're set up like that, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I might even have to…
Kostadis Roussos: I might have to redraw the square if you're… if you move some of the creatures around. I just incorporated one that was near you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, well, one is Helmet of Horror, and the other one is Helmet of Horror, making that just put a B next to it. Oh, wait, now I can do it like this, and I get all… every creature in. What? Wait, so there are two or three? There should be three.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you see different names underneath them? There we go. I see Kelvin Behemoth, Behemoth, and some of them doesn't have a name and personal one. Yeah, so Helman, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so Julia, that's… Yes. One moment, or…
Kostadis Roussos: But in the spaceship orbit, it's gonna be thoroughs. What? In the spaceship orbit, I'm gonna be killing thoroughs. No, you want to put a B, because they do different damage.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, yeah, I know. I'll just… I'll take care of this, don't worry about it. Alright, so we put… there's no stats for it, that's what I'm trying to tell you.
Kostadis Roussos: Excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: I should have played this for your next clear thing.
Kostadis Roussos: It brings it now.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so if I drop out right here, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: The reaction of every fire guy in the room right now.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: And then we can do the ones in a second.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, with stone drink, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, now every creature, there is the… They all have to make… Wait, I was thin…
Kostadis Roussos: Are we ready to start the conduct? Yes. Everybody has to make a… If they're… Fire Giant doesn't have to, but the other three have to make a beefy 19 for strength. Where do we start?
Kostadis Roussos: We're good days? Everybody… Hold on, we'll start at the top of the initiative, where… So, I have a 20. So, I could eat this.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, we can do it the following way. We can start, we can assume that Agritas, we can give Felcor the first action.
Kostadis Roussos: Student will give us a prepared action, and then… Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So I cast the slow. Okay. So, fire trans… make the slow savings flow for those 3, it's a DC19.
Kostadis Roussos: Have you seen MQ? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Spence.
Kostadis Roussos: Do they make it on their turn, or do they make it…
Kostadis Roussos: Make it now, and then every turn has to make it again.
Kostadis Roussos: Or else take 3D6 points, and they take 36 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: I ruled very well. Really? Yes, I ruled this. 15, a 17, a 19. Two of them are… no, that's what I've ruled, I haven't checked their abilities yet. Oh, but
Kostadis Roussos: It's fine, I only cared about one of them.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't care about the other guys you're trying to kill the fire giant.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, all three of them made it. Lovely.
Kostadis Roussos: So what happens to you? Noth, track, hold on, so you can stay in saying that we have to re-roll.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so used currently. Oh!
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. He's currently…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you need 6 blocks of damage. And he takes one? 6 flights of blood to me, let me roll that. One cool out.
Kostadis Roussos: Wow, he takes 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: This is not looking good for the good guys. Oh, it's fine. We have three attacks with Angel. Do you know the one? Come on. Me? No, the frag thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's good. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so how much points of damage? Barley?
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: It's fine. The point of that spell isn't to do damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, comprehensive damage?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. The point of that spell, the Fire Giant can't exactly move anywhere without being trapped. Basically, the Fire Giant is gonna be forced to spend a bunch of turns in there, and the chance that we get it stopped again and again… Of course, he does have a plus 8 for strength.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine. Okay, alright, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, who goes next? Can I… I invite you to invite the fire. Dad, Dad, can I end up… can I end my, surprise turn by going over…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me have this owlbear start here, and telling the fire giant to… we're gonna… we're going to try and flee what the owlbear flee knew, we're going to…
Kostadis Roussos: And then once he… Do you want to also tell them that you, you freed, Skora and stuff? Yeah. So you're going to tell him about the whole… Yeah, not the whole, that's the anticipated. Like, yeah, just a quick gist of what… No, the quick gist? The quick gist of, like, you know, let the… I'll better free you, and then go, and then go, and then help us.
Kostadis Roussos: Back then? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the entire reason we did this plant, so that I had time to basically… No, no, no, I get it, I get it, I'm just trying to…
Kostadis Roussos: Can be elder-free.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I've decided, yes. I'm gonna pass Blinko myself to go.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, roll a DC-17 strength check for the outbear.
Kostadis Roussos: So, spamster?
Kostadis Roussos: 17.
Kostadis Roussos: The owlbearer shatters the stone giant's shackles. I call it the go for your friend.
Kostadis Roussos: The stone giant, stand up.
Kostadis Roussos: Rather than the Stone Jen.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Yeah, yeah. There's no free, he gets, doesn't get an action. Okay, next.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you all… is everybody done? Are these sort of been impacting the sort of… All the Falkour, the items. Alright, so Folkor. Now, who's next?
Kostadis Roussos: I know, because Felker goes, now you do all your reactions and initiate the order. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I'm guessing we'll start. Yes. Oh, you have a fan, bad boy.
Kostadis Roussos: Good to know.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, as long as your friend doesn't know.
Kostadis Roussos: So, what?
Kostadis Roussos: What a tater will do… of Mo.
Kostadis Roussos: with everything.
Kostadis Roussos: Last February 4… Hoyo.
Kostadis Roussos: You better roll a cockle.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you don't wear a balance.
Kostadis Roussos: Production is your bed.
Kostadis Roussos: What is the 12th time?
Kostadis Roussos: That's a bit. Yeah, 30, 30, that's a bit. Okay, so we have to complete all that. Come back when you have the answers. For roll again, roll again, because, forget it.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I knew the advantage is the way you put the picture.
Kostadis Roussos: Mmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, and by the way, Ronkins should use speargons.
Kostadis Roussos: Just, like, instant spirit guiding it up, dude.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna get the installation, probably is not gonna cast again at least 7. We should get…
Kostadis Roussos: We should have all the… that… I'm gonna have the stone giants come up, because I don't want you in packing, like, the two fire giants next to us, because I think,
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, I might… I don't know, should I… because the Fire Giants will leave once their king is dead, right? Yes. So should I have those stone giants attack those fire giants?
Kostadis Roussos: Or should I have them come up to the King Fire Giant? There's a physical space problem. It won't fit? Yes, plus the Fire Giants have crossbows and ranged weapons. So they'll just have them attack? It's up to you. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: in, almost done, you know?
Kostadis Roussos: Only 20?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm not sure if that's the correct one, because we have the local teammates sounds good.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, it doesn't go perfectly good.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, that's the one. Yeah, it was a critical, so it's 54 grams total.
Kostadis Roussos: 6 and 4. How much did you roll for the line of error?
Kostadis Roussos: 9.
Kostadis Roussos: Kidding me! Ouch. You kissed me!
Kostadis Roussos: You have one job!
Kostadis Roussos: How much… how many golds died do you get for the flight together?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, great.
Kostadis Roussos: Even on a 15 time zone.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so not… what did it down to do now?
Kostadis Roussos: Stanton… 92.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that is… oh, wow.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's Diane's turn. Oh, that's easy. I immediately just actively search it up. Wait, we're in the reaction. In the reaction, can we do the prototypes for acting, or no? No.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I cannot do that yet. Wait, but the fire giant goes last, so I can't make a saving throw again, until we all get an attack.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no third component, so if it's granted, there's due.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. It's about being spent.
Kostadis Roussos: Brown Wing will start with… Guiding both.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I was thinking about Guardian of State.
Kostadis Roussos: But there are already paid resources, like, there.
Kostadis Roussos: Ugh.
Kostadis Roussos: We used all that. Like, it's a classic. We want to look up… the goal is the one for this entire thing.
Kostadis Roussos: What's better.
Kostadis Roussos: I was really glad to make, but there's too many… Pretty interesting idea.
Kostadis Roussos: So, decided we'll be talking about self-programming.
Kostadis Roussos: DC surgeon with a particular approach. Alright, four of them, right?
Kostadis Roussos: 3 of them, I don't think number…
Kostadis Roussos: That is 70 or 40 for your business?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me first just, like, check tweets, let me just check if they're immune or resistant to…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, is that down to 80?
Kostadis Roussos: Doing a 12 plus a family?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you need 22, because… Excellent.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what is the, effect? What is the spell we'll be testing on?
Kostadis Roussos: Things like this week, early on.
Kostadis Roussos: We wanted to tell you in podcast details.
Kostadis Roussos: I guess already in the other one? Yeah, no, no, it was fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright, I'm not wrong.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so how many 3… how many do I throw? This is… How many is for how many? Two, right? The one we booking up, and the…
Kostadis Roussos: in fighting. First rule was for the king, he blows it, and the second rule was for the Latina, he blows it, okay? So…
Kostadis Roussos: And we're feeling surprised down with reactions.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you burned your reaction. Yeah, no, because she's laughing because she's done 601. We haven't been drilled down heats yet. Yes, yes, yes, of course.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. It's so good!
Kostadis Roussos: We never have to split it up.
Kostadis Roussos: That one.
Kostadis Roussos: We have a street, hero film, or if we're kind of DC.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a good giants to do. They're…
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the Stone John still saw the backing these in the fleet?
Kostadis Roussos: Let's, let's, let's get to… let's get through one thing at a time. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you guys all done? For our reactions, yes. For a surprise round. Everybody did it. Okay, so now I couldn't just go first.
Kostadis Roussos: At Critus, we use the bone. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: The fire giant wakes up. Could I have left my…
Kostadis Roussos: Could I have left my cannon with one of you guys. That happened to be within 60 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: Excellent. You too, Chuck.
Kostadis Roussos: Do we still have academics of the pipeline?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't… Nick, what is the condition of the average black tentacle sleeps in the…
Kostadis Roussos: Your screen.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the strain, the condition… Tax rules against you have been addressed.
Kostadis Roussos: Excellent.
Kostadis Roussos: All about valid links.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you just do 36 proof of damage?
Kostadis Roussos: I think I've been to more.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you know a critical? I get it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Because of red pots.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I did 4 tickets for peso.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh! I'm going to walk away. Why don't you guys tell me when therapy planning counter ends in less than one round? Let's… I think it's over, if Aquitas hits more than 21 people right now, like the giant's there.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, come on.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, come on, this would be so funny.
Kostadis Roussos: Bid signing? Yes! Oh, poor, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Wow, yes, it was one key point. Absolutely.
Kostadis Roussos: healthcare utilizing.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I have an interesting piece to make. Actually, no, I'm back with you, because I'm…
Kostadis Roussos: Not in Kent, it's not too far away, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: Do not count me out yet. No, no, no, no, no. I can still do… You can… please do it.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not enough of an opportunity to attack us.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't y'all have a couple… I have a couple uses of vicious monsters.
Kostadis Roussos: Look, Daniel has that too, and he's up next. Oh, please, thrill of God. Please do it.
Kostadis Roussos: Please kill a vacation doctor! Please do it! We will try, I'm not saying we can do it, but we will try. What's the Fire Drive's, wisdom?
Kostadis Roussos: Dad, Mr. Fire Giant's wisdom.
Kostadis Roussos: Not very high.
Kostadis Roussos: And you have the second… doesn't it the second attack of just punching in? No, no, if you cast the spell, it's a full action. Can you get… can you have a bonus action on punch?
Kostadis Roussos: Anyway, please continue. Sorry. But I'm gonna… I'm gonna cast Blink on myself.
Kostadis Roussos: Should I give up, or should I just leave it alone?
Kostadis Roussos: I might do blunt, because it's really useful for me to just not have to do anything.
Kostadis Roussos: alright, so then we're gonna… we're gonna cast a blink. We're going to… this giant is free, right?
Kostadis Roussos: This one here is free. This one is free, right?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna go 1…
Kostadis Roussos: sick, I'm gonna go here.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna just wait it out for my nuts.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, no, this will all resolve itself by itself, probably, so I'm gonna go… try to bring more stone that.
Kostadis Roussos: Thanks.
Kostadis Roussos: I misspelled constantly my entire action, I can't see it anymore.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, sweet, thank you, everyone.
Kostadis Roussos: You want to come closer and stop killing the other guys? That? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: A random question. Can I just… no, as a bonus action, after spell, or no? Because I can do it after Firebolt, I can use my pistol. Can I use it my,
Kostadis Roussos: Can I use it after casting Boink on myself?
Kostadis Roussos: We still have decisions there, how to convict him a funny and how to kill it with vicious mockery? Yeah, we do it. We kill the Fire Giant King with, vicious mockery. Alright, so… so what is it? What was your impression?
Kostadis Roussos: Nevermind, I'm gonna go… I… I'm gonna go over…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm actually not gonna cast a blink on myself, and I'm just gonna go run over and free another giant. Okay, use Ape's tools.
Kostadis Roussos: If you have them.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, did I, where do I have to roll sleight of hand? A sleight of hand, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Natural one.
Kostadis Roussos: I got this! Alright. I'm gonna just kind of stay, like, right up close. I'm gonna tell the giant, yo, can I, like, just stay right next to your foot for a sec? Yeah, okay, so the giants… Can I have partial cover top of that? Like, I'm trying to stay, like, right under. You can, like, move over here, and, like, or you can move behind the rocks, like… Yeah. I'm gonna assume that you can, like… Yeah, I'm good, good, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? That, please. Alright, so hold on. Number 3, Steady Home.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's up? Who's up next? I don't pay, but it's still…
Kostadis Roussos: In prison, right? Freedom, yeah. So he rolls the strike check.
Kostadis Roussos: he can shatter the chains, he shatters the chains. He is now free, so he's now free. Okay, so he can move to this chart.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me move this way.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's next? Timoth Nabuki.
Kostadis Roussos: Myth number two, we'll just take a swipe at Broncrap.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you're going to use it, but… Oopsie.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Very common. Done.
Kostadis Roussos: It's got PD20.
Kostadis Roussos: The 17… what is, Brightler doing? What is wrong? And the first one hits.
Kostadis Roussos: does…
Kostadis Roussos: That's 15 points of damage, plus an additional… 1110… I'm pretty terrible.
Kostadis Roussos: 20 pumps of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Constitution, same throw for, concentration. DC10.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's a concentration saving throne by Willing for a constitution.
Kostadis Roussos: 14. Okay. You made your constitution saving draft. Then, again, it's the Rakuten of Things.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, the beginning is finished. Okay, number one is done. And is she gonna try to embrace number 2, or cut our finger?
Kostadis Roussos: in, he runs over there and attempts to break his compatriot's pains.
Kostadis Roussos: He does, so all the giants earns them free.
Kostadis Roussos: And the move 10 more feet that way. All right. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: We have to say, I don't
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, I can listen.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you gonna try to kill it with a vicious mockery? I'm trying to find a song about this exact thing, and I can't…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, come on, reading!
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: So that's like, this is not going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I do? Yeah. Take a look.
Kostadis Roussos: you have to do a DC14 Wisdom Savings.
Kostadis Roussos: The king dies as a…
Kostadis Roussos: He's dead.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure. Focus.
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know, I want to hear the… OH MY GOD! Wait, wait, wait!
Kostadis Roussos: hard to stand.
Kostadis Roussos: It's your turn. What do you… Stand double.
Kostadis Roussos: I taught don't, don't do this!
Kostadis Roussos: Keep going.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the first way to go.
Kostadis Roussos: 24 periods, no longer a challenge.
Kostadis Roussos: I've had much more American.
Kostadis Roussos: And, but organic stretching, pizza bears are white, he's dead.com.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, we really need to distance.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, can we, say that for a bit?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay. Wait, wait, what do you say to it? What do you mean with it? No, no, no, mission block you, like, you're making fun of it, and it takes care of it. What can you say to it? This is like… Kill me now.
Kostadis Roussos: That's what they need.
Kostadis Roussos: No, he's not gonna see it. There's only so much we can ask. All right. Okay. Arl, thank you for committing to the bid.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you for committing to the bit of meeting vicious locker room. Yes, of course. All right, okay. So, what happens next?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Albert.
Kostadis Roussos: However, yes, I mean, what do we do now? What do we have to live, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, right now there's two fire giants. That the Stone Giant's gonna fight? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you have to leave, somehow.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the only problem is we have to…
Kostadis Roussos: See what they tell the guy we're gonna do.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes?
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see… All variables fast.
Kostadis Roussos: Waits? The Algar just waits? I waits.
Kostadis Roussos: Question, because he was put in touch with him, does he have to really look around for movement? Oh, yeah, yeah, so he gets advantage on his throw. Alright, strength? Was it… what did I have to beat for the average tentacle Snake?
Kostadis Roussos: 19. Failed.
Kostadis Roussos: And for…
Kostadis Roussos: He makes it. 13 points of damage! It gives half damage, though. Yes. But it's still giving up.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, what? 13. 13.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not a damaging spell, but it's restrained, so you have…
Kostadis Roussos: Like, the point of the spell was so that you had an advantage on it.
Kostadis Roussos: and literally drop it in, you know, in… That'd be unfair.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold on, I'm just trying to think. Actually, I was gonna roll something to see if I did the test test, but…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, let's stop.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's think of the car loans…
Kostadis Roussos: Are you trying to decide what Bromden's doing? Oh, Bromden does Garden of Fates.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, but then he loses his concentration.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Guardians of Faith is a concentration spell. It isn't?
Kostadis Roussos: Hello, man.
Kostadis Roussos: Doesn't open.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't think so.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll take your word for it.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, let me say, but…
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's no consultation doesn't need consultation, sorry. What? Yeah, okay. He heads us into the towers.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, I can't believe we did that. Alright, so you put…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm gonna put it here, so we'll attack all the pictures, so every patient has to do… Yeah, I know, I read a little bit. This is the reaction of the fire giant.
Kostadis Roussos: One sec.
Kostadis Roussos: bring the back pill. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you have to run three 17 the same curve. I do? Yes, for all the… Hold on, let's just make sure it's on… when is that?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: It's… it has to start, it's on its turn.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not now. Oh, it's on the Christmas plant? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, who's, who's up next?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know. I hope I don't see that.
Kostadis Roussos: I just… I just read it, it said, a large spectral garden… make sure you're reading the Player's Handbook 24 Edition.
Kostadis Roussos: 2014. No, 2024. Oh, I have the 20th…
Kostadis Roussos: 14 spells. So, I don't know if Cassie can shoot it, if you can see the presentation more.
Kostadis Roussos: No concentration center, so… That's why. The only thing that changes is when you move Zoom up.
Kostadis Roussos: Look, so at the start of the creatures turn, or when it enters in space? Huh?
Kostadis Roussos: So, design for… by design number one.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, gang, number one.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, thank you, Carl.
Kostadis Roussos: There it is.
Kostadis Roussos: I assume it's this guy…
Kostadis Roussos: He does 21… he does 40 to… 62 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: On the giant Stone Giant. 62. Yes, on Stone Giant number in there.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, feeling.
Kostadis Roussos: Congrats.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, who's the tackle one?
Kostadis Roussos: Fire that one on Stone Guide. I think it's actually Stone Guide number 3.
Kostadis Roussos: And then… Yeah, another thing. Right. Then, Stone Giant number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: We're now free…
Kostadis Roussos: So it picks up a rock and throws it at Stone Giant, a fire giant number 3.
Kostadis Roussos: I think it was basically impossible.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, let's…
Kostadis Roussos: Care about what the Zionists do. Oh, the other two side giants are down. Well, you will in a second.
Kostadis Roussos: Why? Takes 15 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: 15 or 15? 15. Is this proper time to use it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so let's… how about this? I'm gonna… how about this? We're gonna do this. Fire giants do 60 points of damage each round.
Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giants do… Sometimes… Appreciate you.
Kostadis Roussos: Just so we can keep track of it. I think it's 60, and…
Kostadis Roussos: The other guys do, not only…
Kostadis Roussos: is it 3v8 plus X and more?
Kostadis Roussos: 24, 38 divided by 250 plus an inch. Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so it does 30 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, 30. Yes, when it brings to the tax. Alright, so just deduct the hit points.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, remember, you guys promised to help free the Giants.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you did. That's why I said you're going to care about this. Okay, so, build it forward, next. I'm like, well, I don't care about this, okay, well, then I guess you don't… alright. He has to roll.
Kostadis Roussos: This week, 19, 20 seconds, and this week, 17th. No, he doesn't… no, it's not in the rain. Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Fails both.
Kostadis Roussos: Phase 12, so it explained it from the plugin. Okay. Yeah. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Nate, comments on me.
Kostadis Roussos: And, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, by the way, if it's, restrained, you can have most advantage to enroll with anybody needed that. Okay, well, it was both saving cards. Actually, it, it, it is not both loaded, it, yes. 12 points of damage. 12 points of damage?
Kostadis Roussos: Did you mark the 12 points? No. And you marked the 20? Yeah. Alright. This is probably my most effective plan yet.
Kostadis Roussos: That insight number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just trying to think if, the Helm Horde… well, he can actually attack this round.
Kostadis Roussos: He has an advantage on attack. I know, but I just…
Kostadis Roussos: I just, I just see, does he, does he have a ranged attack?
Kostadis Roussos: If you move, it's difficult terrain. Oh, it could move, right? It's difficult terrain. It's not restrained. It's restraint? No, no, it's difficult terrain. A little bit has a restraint conditioned with…
Kostadis Roussos: If he's got… if he blows the saving throw, he's restrained. Otherwise, it's a restrained… Yeah. It's a difficult terrain. Yes. Okay, cool, so he blew his saving throws, and he's restrained. Yes. Oh my god! That's what I'm about to check. Are we just farming them now?
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, thanks for giving me that spell, by the way.
Kostadis Roussos: I did not… this was not my idea.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I just, like, I… Are you guys having fun? Yeah. Alright, thanks. I don't… in that case, this is a great… this is a great session. All right. So, finish this comment and be done, or… Yeah, we should, because I have to go for a run. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Giant, fire, number 2. Wait, does he have a long clearance of that? No, it does not. Oh, we're moving on to now.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Fire Giant number 2 does, 60 points of damage…
Kostadis Roussos: Your leader's dead, by the way, stop! Yeah, but, but, fuck, giants hate each other.
Kostadis Roussos: So they're gonna attack us, they're gonna fight each other. Yes, but you made a promise to the stone giant king that you would free his slaves.
Kostadis Roussos: I shouldn't have… Why did I… I told the Giants not to attack each other.
Kostadis Roussos: Anyways, but anyway, so… dude, that was a cute two or five, dude! I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: I didn't want to kill two more… Just for the record, the other plan, when you killed him, showed the head, you know, he's dead, maybe everybody runs away, it would have been fine, but anyway, keep going.
Kostadis Roussos: Tried to do some secrets.
Kostadis Roussos: 60 and then 30. It's 60 points of damage, yeah. Cool. To fire… so stone giant number 1.
Kostadis Roussos: 60, okay?
Kostadis Roussos: then it's basically number one. English number one.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, begin at number 1. I made a saving throw.
Kostadis Roussos: the… the second one. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: But there's only 3 of these attacks we've done, right? So, this is the last one, yes? No, it's the second one. Oh, okay, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: He blows it, takes 20 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: And half from that much of the growth, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No. Because he made his input. So he steps over here, so that's 10 movement.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: And… 50, now 5'10?
Kostadis Roussos: There's this body in the way. Yeah, he walked around. Alright, 20, it's, he gets here, and he is now going to hit that.
Kostadis Roussos: 14, what's your armor cost? 21. That's the miss. 14, that's another miss. Alright. Also, roadmap for the split jacket. Oh, dude, I… 2D20 has advantage on that.
Kostadis Roussos: And he blows it!
Kostadis Roussos: Much damage?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I think.
Kostadis Roussos: So, top of the order. Yes. Yes, sir, agreed to start. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: put an arrow and one in a number once, or in one… one other… actually, one of the change one?
Kostadis Roussos: No, do the home fork, because that one's closer to death.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. It says 2018.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, boom… 24…
Kostadis Roussos: If you want to leave it for one of the Spirit Guardians, you can. 24, it's dead? I know. I know there's more people in snow, that doesn't instant burden.
Kostadis Roussos: We are in 12, so one of those beautiful mosquitoes.
Kostadis Roussos: Dead. It's the exact same damage, no. No. Why? Because we don't do the against spawn any damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Snife was 13, 20… Dude, don't you… don't you… do you have a favorite phone?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, those are true, but… second past that.
Kostadis Roussos: That's more difficult.
Kostadis Roussos: Even that test will almost suitable.
Kostadis Roussos: Bob.
Kostadis Roussos: It's just the 1HP. You're vicious mockering yet again. That's what… No, I hope we did, I hope you did what?
Kostadis Roussos: 22 plus 5? Yeah, that's true. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Zoom, can you say smart read again? Oh, probably. Alright, who's next? Stone Giant, I'm afraid. No, me.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, what can we do?
Kostadis Roussos: What do we do? Which one's still captured?
Kostadis Roussos: No one. Everyone's free. Everyone's free. We'll have to start playing with ZAX.
Kostadis Roussos: Or healing the stone giants. One or the other.
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, you have your cold devices.
Kostadis Roussos: I have to get there. Actually, no, I'm gonna just start poking these guys.
Kostadis Roussos: I go here, and I'm just gonna shoot one up. Okay, you climb up on the rock so that you're not shooting. Just gonna poke up my head and be like, haha! Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It… That's a good one.
Kostadis Roussos: 23 points are down for using the cold, device, right? Yeah. Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Then it just goes up back to that day, right? Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: We just poke her head up and poke her head back.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, wait, you've also got your Canon.
Kostadis Roussos: Some members…
Kostadis Roussos: When I poke my head out, I go, like, over here, and then back, and then my hand goes 1, 2, 3…
Kostadis Roussos: And pump, and then forced to lift it up.
Kostadis Roussos: Ignore the fact it's fire damage, I can't change it from a fire set on the gear, so it's…
Kostadis Roussos: 4th damage. Okay. Or 15 plus the damage. Okay, 4th damage. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. And is it being for the four… Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: form. And it gets knocked back by seed. It's not backed by seed?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, which exposes them to another, 15 points of damage from stone bed.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's next? Document number 2. I think that's number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see what Thomas does. How many saving throws. First, he has to make a saving throw against Dexterity. Dexterity? He makes it! No! Okay, so he doesn't take… he takes 10 downs. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And then the Dexterity item blows the, the other one. The strength? The, no, the… oh, wait, he's got… no, he's already made the strength one.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes over here to step outside of the zone,
Kostadis Roussos: He makes a saving throw at the end of the turn, so first he attacks.
Kostadis Roussos: He attacks twice, and this is both times. Alright, now rolls for saving throw.
Kostadis Roussos: And this is the saving throws.
Kostadis Roussos: He's still alive.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. I'm Johnson?
Kostadis Roussos: I keep it interesting. Thanks.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you sort of crack the… I'm doing 39, I'm doing it up right now. Yeah, he's got to turn the 6 feet up. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giant No. 1. Stone Giant No. 1 does 30, 30 points of damage to Fire Giant number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: 13? Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay?
Kostadis Roussos: Dang it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, how much has the number over one types. It's state.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, we'll see. First of all… it's… Welcome aboard.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a new supper.
Kostadis Roussos: Blanky?
Kostadis Roussos: So, that's only 12 peak points.
Kostadis Roussos: Ronkin said something about, you had to be a bar, didn't you?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that's why you don't have a third attack!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, who's next? Hi, this information.
Kostadis Roussos: I didn't have the chance to go over it yet, P.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's next? Albert.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, I think Vicious mockery is a bonus action.
Kostadis Roussos: Can I do this from afar?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you're saying words, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Go Ugly. Oh, it's 665, and it's an action, so I gotta do that. Oh, it's an action, it's not a transaction. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Under… And I don't want to go die.
Kostadis Roussos: Elder charges. Why did you say instead?
Kostadis Roussos: Because that's what owl bears do.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you ask me? Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Is painting number one or not this clear?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, number two, it's got two stone vans.
Kostadis Roussos: Number one's that Bonsai.
Kostadis Roussos: That was too cranky number two, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Blessed Eric, loved ones of Queens.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a miss, that's a hit.
Kostadis Roussos: So, 13 3.2 number… Two, right? 10 o'clock.
Kostadis Roussos: Expects?
Kostadis Roussos: Brumgan. Brumgan.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll…
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it's huge.
Kostadis Roussos: Other than the Stone Giants. Other than the Stone Giants.
Kostadis Roussos: The Stonebrands can, like, move away if they don't want to die, but, like, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: I guess I'm gonna use,
Kostadis Roussos: And what they don't have to do is,
Kostadis Roussos: We're gonna just stop it there, I guess, to the number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you'll have to be able to… similar.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Below the same girl. We're running two pegs.
Kostadis Roussos: That would be… or representatives, for instance.
Kostadis Roussos: I accepted a meme for the product image.
Kostadis Roussos: Doesn't that now? Well, we didn't ask.
Kostadis Roussos: So, real big ones? What? Yeah, no damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Respects?
Kostadis Roussos: 8, fire giant number one. Alright, so Fire Giant No. 1…
Kostadis Roussos: Does, 60 points of damage to stone deck number 3.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay?
Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giant number 2 does 30 points of damage to giant number 2, fire giant number 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Fair.
Kostadis Roussos: Gong Borr… The singular helm of horror.
Kostadis Roussos: It has to make a bunch of second throws. Yes, it has to do with dexterity and the strength.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the strength one, he fails and dies.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. So, Detective is still alive. I'm just saying. All right, who's next? A fire giant.
Kostadis Roussos: Did he miss?
Kostadis Roussos: The Fire Giant, number 2, does 60 on the Stone Giant. notice he has to choose. Now, if it attacks the Stone Giant, 60 points on the Stone Giant. Stone Giant. Number 1.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, who's next?
Kostadis Roussos: the kingdom number one. Became with number one. Attacks down. He has to do a saving.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that excitement. Who does?
Kostadis Roussos: Enables? Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Big simple to damage. He attacks twice.
Kostadis Roussos: And the second attack hits, or, reading 10.
Kostadis Roussos: No, but please be careful.
Kostadis Roussos: For 27 points of damage. Okay, then do the boosters and go for the speed of lightning.
Kostadis Roussos: And he mixes a wisdom Saber Girl.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so wait, dying takes 24… 27? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm saving it green.
Kostadis Roussos: And this is put in number 1, right? Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: That takes 15, and now it takes 7, statement, mainly.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I created a third. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I think I'll wait at that… Science, one number two.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, silly. You're so… Relightening hour.
Kostadis Roussos: By lightning arrow?
Kostadis Roussos: So, I'd like to narrow to that.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that number 2 is dead.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, number 2 is dead. Yes, but it's impossible only onboard that company does.
Kostadis Roussos: And that's… The fruit, or fantastic things.
Kostadis Roussos: And headquarters?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Stone's giant, number 3 in the 1.
Kostadis Roussos: They're 3-in-1, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Stone Giant number 3 and 1.
Kostadis Roussos: I still enjoy the new 3 disengages.
Kostadis Roussos: And decides to go overkill.
Kostadis Roussos: Wanna move on?
Kostadis Roussos: Phone Giant No. 1, Smashers, fire giant number 2 for 3 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, fire the stone ground, right? Stone drive, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, and it's diamonds… Fair.
Kostadis Roussos: Boy.
Kostadis Roussos: diagnosticator number one.
Kostadis Roussos: Perspectives… So, for a store panels.
Kostadis Roussos: Third key points, and number one is depth.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: For how many rounds did you spill down? Which one? Oh, one minute, 10 minutes.
Kostadis Roussos: Or we're filmed.
Kostadis Roussos: I wonder if we have kind of stuck outside the room, because we cannot do outside. The long section, or the action?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Can I dismiss it?
Kostadis Roussos: William's fine. You can get out.
Kostadis Roussos: Where our goodness is, she can get out there. Yeah, but I'll explain. You want me to get you out of the cast, I can use the… You can go through Brandrome.
Kostadis Roussos: I can also cast Hole on the Wall.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm just telling you, you can… I can cast a hole in the wall, if that helps.
Kostadis Roussos: You want me to pass the past one?
Kostadis Roussos: No, you don't have the other button.
Kostadis Roussos: How do you do the one-up thing?
Kostadis Roussos: Cool? Yeah, click forward into. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So we're gonna go… Do you? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me give it backwards group.
Kostadis Roussos: older.
Kostadis Roussos: So we have to leave them now.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a deal.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, I need multiple. No.
Kostadis Roussos: Bill Stonejiang sort of dead, or did that.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, brown glue.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, did he skip my turn?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I think we did. Go for it. Sorry, yeah, you know, I could have gone…
Kostadis Roussos: I could've cut- got you guys all out. It's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: We have to steal and protect and feed the fight. Yes, that's why it would have been useful, because I can cast a hole in the wall and you can get through. Well, then I still have to attach, so it wouldn't have a chance to come and attach. I know, you want me to cast the hole in the wall? Yes. Alright, cool, there's now a hole that allows me to get through here.
Kostadis Roussos: Through… from here to here? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that the bonus action or an action?
Kostadis Roussos: That's an action, it's fun. I don't have a heel spell I can use.
Kostadis Roussos: Because of one of the giants who's gonna be dead.
Kostadis Roussos: You have heal spells, you don't think… you have to add the branch to get it, though.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a guy that touch, he'll stop.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I can't… if we have a hole, the brand is gonna go through and… Yeah, that's what I did, that's why there's now a hole, and I just gonna… Okay, where's the hole? It's 20 feet deep, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, 2018, Yeah, this is 20 slip, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, very good.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, come from until number 1.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I think, if you've got, do we have Gander?
Kostadis Roussos: How's a must be a word? No, what's the range for masking word?
Kostadis Roussos: 6 feet, so we're ready to go. Yeah, I agree.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, let's good at number one.
Kostadis Roussos: Never mind, I, I've been blind.
Kostadis Roussos: Mostly billing world.
Kostadis Roussos: is for 38 coupons. I would like. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Cooling number one, right? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I guess it's fired Southern Ontario Planned.
Kostadis Roussos: Fire Giant, number 1.
Kostadis Roussos: And just as Fire Giant number one noticed, you guys didn't notice her, but the Lostra walks in and casts banishment on him.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Okay. The revenants.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Lovely! Right. What a lovely… and screams, where is Dendron?
Kostadis Roussos: Is that a guy who just killed? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll stop here.
Kostadis Roussos: The fire giant is dead.
Kostadis Roussos: Can I say he wasn't the one who killed… We're not remembering.
Kostadis Roussos: It's better.
Kostadis Roussos: Number one did it. The other fire giant did it, that guy did it. We can point to the other guy and say, he did it!
Kostadis Roussos: That's stupid!
Kostadis Roussos: We killed their BPEG too fast and needed something else to do? No, I was thinking, what would she be doing? She would be charging straight addendum.
Kostadis Roussos: That wasn't the fire giant that you needed. That wasn't the fire giant that killed him. Yep, see, that's the key, is that confusion speed to clutch for… again? I can't roll 3 clutch, not 20! Or she figures out that Sullivan… or you could send her back to Sullivan.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't actually owe them anything.
Kostadis Roussos: You know what's a problem with that.
Kostadis Roussos: Because technically, we need a reliability more. Yes!
Kostadis Roussos: But the problem is that it skies.
Kostadis Roussos: Who is the type of parental?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, she's gonna come back. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you, you have options. A good four and a half hour D&D session.
Kostadis Roussos: you know, CQ.